igdb.com 2019-10-13

# Privacy Service

  1. Home
  2. Privacy Policy

Review IGDB.com’s (8 Dudes in a Garage AB, "IGDB") legal and privacy notices for details on how we collect, use and protect your personal information on the website.

Your use of and access to any website or software application owned by IGDB (IGDB Property(ies)') either (i) made available to you directly or indirectly from this website; or (ii) with a direct link to this privacy policy is subject to this privacy policy. This privacy policy explains the data that we collect and how we use it.

We respect your privacy. If you have any privacy concerns or questions about this privacy policy, you can contact us by email at: [privacy@igdb.com](mailto:privacy@igdb.com).

### About Us and This Policy

All references to "we", "us" or "our" refer to 8 Dudes in a Garage AB. 8 Dudes in a Garage AB is incorporated in Gothenburg, Sweden and its principal office is Norra Agatan 2, 416 49. 8 Dudes in a Garage AB is the controller of the personal data you submit to us.

This policy gives you the details of who we are and the details of our privacy policies, including: what data we collect about you when you use IGDB Property; what organization is collecting the information; how the information will be used or disclosed; what choices are available to you regarding collection and use of the data; what security measures are in place to protect your personal information; and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

This policy may be amended from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new privacy policy on this page. You are advised to review this privacy policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this privacy policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

### Your Information: What We Collect, How We Collect It, and How It Is Used

In common with most other websites and on-line services, we collect certain data about your visit to the IGDB Properties. Any data we gather through your use of IGDB Property falls into three categories:

Personal information that you supply to us, such as information you provide when you register (including your e-mail address), create an account, create a user name, register your device, complete a survey, enter a contest, or purchase products or services.

Once you have created an account, you will have the option to fill out a form (all or portions of which may be included in your profile). When you create your profile, we collect personal information about you, such as location, e-mail address, favorite games, etc. which will be stored in order to provide services to you and to conduct activities including, without limitation, using it to process your registration, maintain a profile about you, process your request to receive newsletters and email announcements, or to voluntarily participate in surveys or contests and/or to communicate with you about services and products we think may be of interest to you.

Email addresses are used for identification, inviting new friends to IGDB Properties, searching for and finding friends, general communication, order processing and to send notifications to you. To facilitate searching for and finding friends on the IGDB Properties, IGDB allows users to search for other members using text searches, nick name, email address, and by using other attributes. Users can invite friends to join certain IGDB Properties by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. As part of our service, IGDB stores these email addresses so that the respondents may be added to the friend list of the member sending the invitations and to establish relationships between users.

We process your personal data in order for us to administer and provide your personal account and the features and content that it includes, and when applicable, to fulfil your purchase agreement. The legal basis for processing this data is to fulfill our commitments under the agreement of providing you with your personal account and/or purchase agreement, and our legitimate interest of communicating with you about services and products we think may be of interest to you.

Information such as games you have rated, reviewed, or are following that is collected as you use IGDB Property that becomes identified with your personal information. We process your personal data in order for us to deliver a personalised experience of our services and make an analysis of the data collected for this purpose to further our services towards you, such as show tracking and recommendations. The legal basis for processing this data is to fulfill our commitments under the agreement of providing you with your personal account.

Information that does not directly identify you and is collected as you use IGDB Property, including your IP address, and information gathered with the use of a “cookie”, clear GIFs (which are also sometimes called web bugs or web beacons), browser details and information related to searches or recommendations on IGDB Property. Such information collected includes, without limitation, your browser type, the type of operating system you use, the domain name of your Internet service provider, IP address, which pages and content are browsed, services used and how you have used them, interactions with advertising and content, and other data related to preferences and usage.

We use this information to be able to evaluate, develop and improve our products and services, including, without limitation, to better target advertising and content, (on our and our Partner's websites), to generate statistics and reports and in order to optimize our site and present you with relevant material and for marketing purposes. The legal basis for processing this data is that it is necessary in order to satisfy our and our customers legitimate interest in evaluating, developing and improving our services, products and systems and to receive information and marketing from us.

You may use certain IGDB Property without registering or creating an account. We may nonetheless build a history of your interactions with the IGDB Property even though we don't know who you are. Anonymous user information will be used to generate statistics and comparison data for the benefit of our users. It can also be used for the purpose of market research surveys and marketing, the aggregated results of which can be sold or forwarded to our business partners or customers.

### Advertising

We may use your personal information and non-personal information to serve ads to you via IGDB Property as well as to provide you with promotions, products and services. We may also use third-party advertising companies and other business partners to serve ads on IGDB Property or Partner Sites and provide you with promotions, products and services. These third-party advertising companies and our business partners may be located throughout the world.

These third-party advertising companies and business partners may receive and share with us information relating to the advertisements that they serve you including, without limitation, date and time of ad shown, the banner ad that was shown and your IP address and your interactions with such advertisements. These third-party advertising companies and business partners may use cookies, clear GIFs and anonymous information about your visits to IGDB Property and other websites to measure and improve the effectiveness of their ads, promotions, products and services. This information may also be used for online preference and other targeted marketing purposes. The information received by these third-party advertising companies and business partners is subject to the privacy policies of these third-party advertising companies and business partners. We may be given access to this information by these third-party advertising companies and business partners which we may use for purposes including, without limitation, to better target advertising and content to you and to generate statistics and reports that help us develop our products and services.

We may make certain information about you available to third-party advertising companies and other business partners under agreements between us and those third-party advertising companies and business partners. The third-party advertising companies and business partners will use that information to target advertising to you or provide and market promotions, products and services to you. You can choose not to provide your personal information to advertising companies and business partners at any time by adjusting your preferences in the preference page of the relevant IGDB Property. If you do so we will not provide your personal information from the relevant IGDB Property to third party advertisers or business partners. However where permitted by applicable law, we may still provide them with information that does not directly identify you from which they may send you targeted advertisements.

You may object to the use of your personal data for advertising and marketing purposes at any time. This applies to all advertising purposes and individual actions.

### Personal information and retention of data

IGDB may allow you to set up profiles that may be viewed by other users of the IGDB Properties. To enrich your profile you may chose to include some personal information in your public profile so that other users can identify you. You should only include information in your public profile that you do not mind making publicly available without restriction.

IGDB will keep your personal data for as long as you have an active personal account, as long as there is a purchase agreement or other agreement in force or for as long as it is necessary to fulfil our contractual obligations to do so.

You have the right to terminate your account at any time, if you choose to do so your account will cease to exist and you will be considered inactive. We will keep your personal data if there are any legal requirements to do so or if there is an open dispute.

After your account has been terminated your data will be deleted, unless it can be made anonymous for statistical purposes.

### Cookies

Information about our use of cookies is contained in our "Cookie Policy".

### Security

We use commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information. However, due to the design of the Internet, ever-changing technology and other factors outside of our control, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and our servers will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. We will have no liability for disclosure of personal information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized or unlawful acts of third parties.

You are responsible for the security of your user name, ID and password for any of the IGDB Properties. Please take care when using and storing them.

### Changing Your Personal Information & Preferences

 **Your Right to Choose**

When you register to access certain IGDB Properties, you can let us know that you do not wish to receive announcements from us. You may also later opt out of providing us personal identifiable information by changing your preferences in the set up areas of the relevant IGDB Properties or changing the necessary settings in your profile. For certain IGDB Properties opting out may only be possible if you delete your account for that IGDB Property. If you opt out or do not provide your personal information then some services and features (such as personal information services, recommendations and tracking of ratings and likes and dislikes) may not be available to you or may be deleted. All newsletters and email announcements from us will contain an unsubscribe link that also allows you to opt out at any time from these messages.

 **Review and Correction**

You may review and update the personal information that you have provided us by visiting the relevant set up page of the IGDB Property and updating your account profile.

### Recipients of the personal data

When you provide information to IGDB, that information is collected and maintained either by IGDB or by an authorized agent or contractor of IGDB. We may provide data about our users, traffic patterns, products, services and site information to third-parties (such as vendors, advertisers and our business partners) (‘Partners'), but we will use reasonable efforts to provide it in a form that does not directly identify you.

In other words, when it is necessary for us in order to fulfil our agreement with you, or in order to offer our services and products, we share your personal data with other companies that help us with IT services (web hosting, technical support, maintenance of our IT solution), Marketing and customer care (social media, customer care service providers, media agencies and advertising agencies) and Payment solutions (transaction processing service, payment service providers).

When required by law we share your personal data with government agencies (police, tax authorities or other authorities). Sometimes the companies offering payment solutions, such as banks, are controllers. When your personal data is forwarded to a controller, their privacy policy and terms and conditions are applicable on the processing of your data.

### Other Disclosure of Personal Information

We will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent except (i) as described in this privacy policy, (ii) as required by court order or other government or law enforcement authorities in order to comply with legal process or law, (iii) in the event of a merger where another company has acquired the relevant IGDB Property, (iv) in order to protect against the misuse or unauthorized use of IGDB Property, (v) in order to protect and defend our rights and property, or (vi) in order to protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public.

If IGDB sells assets (or the assets of a division or subsidiary) to another entity, including, without limitation, in the event of bankruptcy, or if IGDB (or a division or subsidiary) is acquired by, or merged with, another entity, IGDB may provide to such entity and/or its affiliates user information (both anonymized and/or aggregate and personal information) that is related to that part of the business that was sold to or merged with the other entity.

### Links to Third Party Websites

IGDB Properties may display links to websites operated by third parties. If you click on a link, the relevant third party operator or others may collect data about you when you visit the linked website. They are responsible for the collection and further processing of such data and we have no control over it. We advise you to check the terms of use and privacy policies of any linked websites you visit to find out what data they are collecting and the purposes for which they process your personal data.

### Overseas Transfers and Processing of Your Information

The personal data that we collect from you is stored within the EU/EEA but may also be transferred to and processed in a country outside of the EU/EEA. Any such transfer of your personal data will be carried out in compliance with applicable laws.

For transfers outside the EU/EEA, we will use Standard Contractual Clauses and Shields or your consent for countries without adequacy decisions from the European Commission.

### Children's Privacy

We do not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children"). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with personal data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected personal data from children under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will take steps to remove that information from our servers.

### Your rights

You have the right to request access to and rectification or erasure of personal data or restriction of processing concerning the data subject, or to object to processing as well as the right to data portability. You have the right to request that your data is not used for direct marketing purposes. You have the right to withdraw consent where such is given, at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.

You have the right to lodge a complaint of our processing of your personal data with the supervisory authority where you live or work, in Sweden it is the Swedish Data Protection Authority.

### Inquiries

If you have any concern about privacy at IGDB, please contact us at [privacy@igdb.com](mailto:privacy@igdb.com) or the address stated above.
